<resources>
    <string name="app_name">E-Light</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id">007</string>

    <string name="floating_action_button">Fab</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact us</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="about__us">About us</string>

    <string name="about_us">
    \t   Overtime, Humanity has Evolved, through the stone age to what we now know as the Jet age, but one thing has remained constant in the Human spirit.\n \n
     \t   It is the thirst to become more than he already is, to Control more than he already does and to connect to Divinity if we believe there is any.\n \n \n
     \t   Sadly we are born and then we are gone. But in between we fail to quench this thirst deep within our soul, Another thing is Certain, we have failed to understand that to become more we must Explore Now. We must Live the moment, we must see that tomorrow is Now Today and soon will become Yesterday. We must keep Moving forward while living our today,\n\n
    \t     We are The Enlightenment Center  (The Elight Center).\n \n
      \t    We believe in a better Tomorrow
    \t     But We believe a better Tomorrow will only be accomplished by a better Today,\n \n
    \t     We believe you can, if you try.\n \n
    \t      We believe life is measured by progress,\n \n
     \t      We believe your progress is Important, this is why we are committed at inspiring you to make progress. This is who we are, it is what we do. \n \n
     \t      We are #TheElightCenter.\n \n
    And we inspire you to make progress\n \n
    Some have lost their Humanity trying to be better humans. Humanity is still Evolving and As we know.\n  \n
    \t    Life is a fast train, you have your ticket now, As you get in Enjoy every bit of your trip, and create influence, impact as ND Memories as These are the only thing people will keep of you. When you alight,
    Once more.\n \n
    \t     We are TheElightCenter, And we inspire you to make progress.\n\n
    \t      Success is Certain\n \n
     &#169; TheElightCenter 2018 \n\n
      \t    \t  \t   Keep Progressing.</string>
</resources>
